crcpress.com 2014-11-21

# CRC Press Online - Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

##### Taylor & Francis Group, LLC Privacy Policy Statement

This online Privacy Policy is designed to tell you about how we collect and use information so that as a user of the site, you can make an informed choice about using the website identified by the URL www.crcpress.com and/or any website that is automatically redirected to the website operated by Taylor & Francis Group, LLC.

##### What Information Do We Collect?

When you register yourself on this website, we ask for your full name and email address. When purchasing products from the website, we ask you to provide shipping and billing addresses, including your country, state or province, and postal code. All credit card information is stored and used according to the rules laid out by the Payment Card Industry Digital Security Standard (PCI DSS). You can find more information about this standard in the [PCI Quick Reference Guide (link is external) __](https://www.pcisecuritystandards.org/pdfs/pci_ssc_quick_guide.pdf).

##### Use of Personal Data

Any personal data that you give us will be treated with the utmost care and security. It will not be used in ways to which you have not consented.

The personal data we collect is used to provide you with the services you have requested or the products you have purchased, or to respond to an inquiry that you have made. We use certain third party service providers to assist us in providing these services to you; for example, email alerting.

The personal data we acquire via the email alert service will not be used for marketing purposes except where you have indicated on the registration page that we may do so.

We will not sell, rent, or loan any personal data or identifiable information collected on this website, except that we may pass or sell your personal data outside our corporate group to third parties in the event that we sell the whole or part of our business.

When you send email or other communications to CRC Press or participate in virtual focus groups or online surveys, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests, and improve our services.

The information collected from this website will be stored for as long as is required for the uses stated above.

##### Users' Right to Opt Out

If you do not want to continue to receive email communications from us, please let us know by logging in and using the online form to opt out.

##### Grace Period

Should you request that we amend or suppress records containing your personal data, we will attempt to do so as promptly as is practical; however, you may receive communications for a transitional period while we process your records.

##### Use of Cookies and Logfiles

A cookie is a small text file written to an individual's hard drive that contains the user ID. We do not place other personal information inside the cookie.

The use of cookies is now widespread by websites in order to track traffic flow. From time to time, we may use cookies to enable us to offer certain time-saving features to our users. These may be used to administer the website, track users' movements and actions, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. The information gathered would then be used to improve the website and users' experiences.

We maintain server logs that may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request, and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser.

For more information visit our cookies page.

##### Hyperlinks

This website contains links to other websites, including those websites of companies within the Taylor & Francis Group, LLC which form part of the Academic & Scientific, Professional, and Commercial Divisions. Their inclusion should not be taken to imply any endorsement or validation by us of the content of said websites. Taylor & Francis Group, LLC is not responsible for the privacy practices, nor do we accept any liability in connection with the content of such websites, including those of our group companies, which have their own privacy policies tailored for the particular business practices and sectors in which they operate.

##### Changes/Updates to Privacy Policy

In order to keep up with changing legislation and best practices, we may revise this Privacy Policy at any time without notice; so please check back periodically so that you are aware of any changes.

##### Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or feel that your privacy has been compromised, please contact us at [techsupport@crcpress.com](mailto:techsupport@crcpress.com) or at this address:

 **Privacy Policy  
Taylor & Francis Group, LLC**  
6000 Broken Sound Parkway NW  
Boca Raton, FL 33487  
U.S.A.
